<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Clay County News Center</title><link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link><description>Combined Local and Regional Updates</description>
        <item>
            <title>CISNE CLINIC REOPENS</title>
            <link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link>
            <description>[County News - General News] 1/2/26
Horizon Healthcare announced that the Cisne Clinic will reopen and resume full operations on Monday.
The clinic was temporarily closed to allow for necessary facility maintenance and improvements to ensure a safe, comfortable, and welcoming en...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>🏦 COUNTY FAIR QUEEN PAGEANT</title>
            <link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link>
            <description>[County News - State News] 1/2/26
The 2026 Miss Illinois County Fair Queen Pageant will be held on Saturday, January 17th and Sunday the 18th in Springfield.  Clay County Fair Queen Olivia Haun will be honored at a sendoff party at the State Bank Suites Sunday from 1 to 3 pm.
...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>🚨 WAYNE COUNTY SHERIFFS REPORT</title>
            <link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link>
            <description>[County News - Police Report] 1/2/26
Wednesday at approximately 4:30 pm Wayne County Sheriff’s Deputies were called to a residence in Cisne on the report of a possible domestic disturbance.
When the first Deputy arrived, they heard a female inside the residence screaming for help...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>HO HO HOLIDAY HIGHLIGHT CONTEST</title>
            <link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link>
            <description>[Flora - General News] 1/2/26
Ho Ho Holiday Highlight entries are now due.  Each day in December a different business was featured, listeners were asked to keep track of those business’s then send us your list of all 31 highlighted business’s.
Your completed contest entry ...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>PEAK SCHOLARSHIP</title>
            <link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link>
            <description>[County News - General News] 1/2/26
Frontier Community College and Olney Central College are pleased to announce the Kenton Peak Scholarship, a $1,000 annual award supporting students pursuing para-medical fields, emergency medical response, and other healthcare-related programs...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>🏦 GROCERY TAX GONE?</title>
            <link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link>
            <description>[Flora, Louisville, Clay City - State News] 1/2/26
Illinois’ statewide 1% grocery tax went away yesterday, although many people continue to pay it at the local level.
Data compiled by the Illinois Municipal League shows that 656 municipalities, a little more than half of the state’s municipali...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>🚌 GINGERBREAD HOUSE DISPLAY</title>
            <link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link>
            <description>[Flora - School News] 1/2/26
Time is running out to vote for your favorite Flora High School Foods Class Gingerbread house.  Displays are at the Flora Public Library through Tuesday.  The students were asked to make houses from children’s books.
There are 30 different hou...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>🏦 RURAL HEALTHCARE AWARD</title>
            <link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link>
            <description>[County News - State News] 1/2/26
Illinois has been awarded $193,418,216 per year for five years through the $50 billion federal Rural Healthcare Transformation Program (RHTP) fund, which will be utilized to expand equitable access to healthcare and to eliminate barriers to ca...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>FARM PAYMENTS ANNOUNCED</title>
            <link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link>
            <description>[County News - General News] 1/2/26
Farmers are now learning how much aid they can expect to receive from a $12 billion package that President Donald Trump announced earlier this month.
The US Department of Agriculture released the figures on Wednesday for how much aid per acre ...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>🚨 The ReVue</title>
            <link>https://supportmylocalcommunity.com/clay-county-news-center/</link>
            <description>[County News - Police Report] 12/31/25
Today on the ReVue I talk with the musical group the BurmaShavers, Steve Folwler and Jerry Wilson about their music.
Burma Shavers.wav
Booking information is available at theburmashavers@hotmail.com...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item></channel></rss>